Guide to the James A. Roberts Papers
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Papers, Accession ARCH-1999-290
  - Iceland: maps, flyers, publications 1990-1994 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Iceland: EIR & related reports, articles, memoranda (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Iceland: VHS videotape- Soil Conservation on Iceland (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Hungary: Slovak Material 1995 (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Hungary: 1991-1992 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Hungary: reports 1991 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - UTR reports “3rd RD & Current Chrono”: proposed conceptual design report draft 1996 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - UTR: slides & index- erosion (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - UTR: Roberts working notes 1996 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - UTR: Phase I report 1995 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - UTR: conceptual design report 1996 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - UTR: conceptual design report 1997 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - UTR: to dos (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - UTR: CTC 1996-1998 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Miscellaneous project reports: photographs, negatives, charts, maps 1992 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - 04692.00.302 Wetlands Mitigation related documents (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - 04692.00.303b Wetlands Mitigation report 11/18/1992 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - 04692.00.303d Wetlands Mitigation report 11/8/1992 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - 04692.00.303a Wetlands Mitigation report 11/23/1992 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - 04692.00.304 CEQA process- MDP EIR (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - 04692 B&J Sanitary Landfill Project 1993 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - 04692.00.400 COE NW 26 Permit 1993 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - 04692.00.401 Bird Hazards 1992-1994 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - 04692.00.401 Bird Hazards Reports (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - 04692.00.402 Revegetation (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - 04692.00.403 Weed Monitoring (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - 04692.00.404 Reclamation Plan (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - 04692.00.405 Swainson’s Hawk (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - 04692.00.406 Findings, Staff Report on FEIR & Permits (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - 04692.00.7 Screen Tree (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - 04692.00.8 Emergent Wetland B&J (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - 04692.00.8 Emergent Wetland Contract (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - 04692.00.9 Bird Monitoring (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - 00693 Hualien University Taiwan (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - 03193 Slovak EIR Law (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - 05493 Tallin Botanical Garden, Estonia 1994 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - 00494.00.000 Roderick v. Folsom, general 1992 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - 00494.00.100 Roderick v. Folsom contract (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - 94031 Franchise Tax Board 1994 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - 03194 Franchise Tax Board contract (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - 06092/00293 Orange City 1993 (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - 06092.00.120 Orange City Contract (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - 06092.00.400 Revised EIR 1989 (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - Alaska: State Parks 1997 (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - Plymouth/Shenandoah Springs 1996 (Box 22, Folder 24)
  - Hawaii: Geothermal Prospects EIS 1993 (Box 22, Folder 25)
  - Hawaii: Ocean Recreation Management 1989 (Box 22, Folder 26)
  - Hawaii: OEQC Bulletins, correspondence, reports 1991-1992 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Asia & S.E. Asia: File Index (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Asia & S.E. Asia: general 1993-1996 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Asia & S.E. Asia: U.S.-Asia Environmental Partnership (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Asia & S.E. Asia: Japan Earthquake Consulting 1997 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Asia & S.E. Asia: CAL-SEA Business Council 1996 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Asia & S.E. Asia: Hong Kong (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Asia & S.E. Asia: Indonesia (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Asia & S.E. Asia: Indonesia Technology Visit 1996 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Asia & S.E. Asia: NBD: China 1992-1997 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Asia & S.E. Asia: 94036 China Asia Fund 1994 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Asia & S.E. Asia: India (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Asia & S.E. Asia: Japan: COE Tokyo (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Asia & S.E. Asia: NBD Korea (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Asia & S.E. Asia: Malaysia (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Asia & S.E. Asia: Philippines General (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Asia & S.E. Asia: Philippines U.S-AID Agency for International Development (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Asia & S.E. Asia: Philippines Diaz-Supermax (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Asia & S.E. Asia: Philippines PRMPD (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - Asia & S.E. Asia: Business Opportunity Seminar (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - Asia & S.E. Asia: Singapore (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - Asia & S.E. Asia: Taiwan- mountains (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - Asia & S.E. Asia: Taiwan Wen –Shan Huang (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - Asia & S.E. Asia: Taiwan general (Box 23, Folder 24)
  - Asia & S.E. Asia: Thailand (Box 23, Folder 25)
  - Asia & S.E. Asia: Vietnam (Box 23, Folder 26)
  - Asia & S.E. Asia: Australia (Box 23, Folder 27)
  - NAEP (National Association of Environmental Professionals) – Roberts Presidential Files #3, 2-7/1998: newsletters, correspondence (Box 23, Folder 28)
  - NAEP Roberts: newsletters, correspondence (Box 23, Folder 29)
  - NAEP Roberts: newsletters, correspondence 1997-1998 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - NAEP Roberts: newsletters, correspondence 6/1998 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - NAEP Roberts: newsletters, correspondence 1998 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - NAEP Roberts: newsletters, correspondence 1998 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - NAEP Roberts: newsletters, correspondence 1998 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - NAEP Roberts: newsletters, correspondence 2-3/1998 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - NAEP Roberts Presidential Files #2: International general 1995-1996 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - NAEP Roberts: ISO (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - NAEP Roberts: ECO Environmental Careers Organization 1995 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - NAEP Roberts: NEHA National Environmental Health Association (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - NAEP Roberts: NAEM (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - NAEP Roberts: NIE National Institute for the Environment (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - NAEP Roberts: membership ideas (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - NAEP Roberts: NAEP news (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - NAEP Roberts: officers/election 1996-1997 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - NAEP Roberts: NREP (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - NAEP Roberts: other environmental Organizations (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - NAEP Roberts: policy committee (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - NAEP Roberts: Dennis Poulson (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - NAEP Roberts: Board meeting 1997 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - NAEP Roberts: President’s Message (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - NAEP Roberts: publications (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - NAEP Roberts: Strange Things file (includes global warming, ozone layer research) (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - NAEP Roberts: Tom Cuba, sustainable Development (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - NAEP Roberts: VISTA (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - NAEP Roberts: TNT Tools & Techniques (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - NAEP Roberts: ABCEP/CEP certification review effort (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - NAEP Roberts: President’s Council (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - NAEP Roberts Presidential Files #1: Articles of Incorporation/Bylaws 1997 (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - NAEP Roberts: Academic Centers for Environmental Excellence (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - NAEP Roberts: Air & Waste Management Association (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - NAEP Roberts: Business & Final Plan (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - NAEP Roberts: CEP materials (Box 25, Folder 23)
  - NAEP Roberts: Career Encounters (Box 25, Folder 24)
  - NAEP Roberts: Maryland (Box 25, Folder 25)
  - NAEP Roberts: Meeting 12/1997 (Box 25, Folder 26)
  - NAEP Roberts: Donna Carter (Box 25, Folder 27)
  - NAEP Roberts: Chapters (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - NAEP Roberts: Committees General (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - NAEP Roberts: Mission Statements working groups & committees (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - NAEP Roberts: Conference Coordination (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - NAEP Roberts: Corporation working group (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - NAEP Roberts: Elections (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - NAEP Roberts: EMS Environmental Management Systems (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - NAEP Roberts: Executive Committee (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - NAEP Roberts: Fellows & Awards (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - NAEP Roberts: Past President’s Luncheon (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - NAEP Roberts: Monthly Reports 1997 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - NAEP Roberts: Publishing- bids, etc. (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - NAEP Roberts: Fundraising (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - NAEP Roberts: GMV Conference 1997 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - NAEP Roberts: International Academy Santa Barbara (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - NAEP Roberts: International Committee Internet 1996 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - NAEP correspondence: Blackwell 1997 (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - NAEP correspondence: previous minutes & related 1997 (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - NAEP correspondence: Zirzow (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - NAEP correspondence: Executive Secretary (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - NAEP correspondence: Addresses (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - NAEP correspondence: Rocky Mountains Chapter (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - NAEP correspondence: Dennis Poulson, managing director 1996-1997 (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - NAEP correspondence: Executive Committee Book 1 1996-1997 (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - NAEP correspondence: American People Ambassador Program (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - NAEP correspondence: Board Meeting 5/1997 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - NAEP correspondence: CEHP General Committee (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - NAEP correspondence: Conference, Chang visit 1996 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - NAEP correspondence: CEHP contract, final (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - NAEP correspondence: CEHP (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - NAEP correspondence: Conference Committee 1996 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - NAEP correspondence: Duck Committee Book 2 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - NAEP correspondence: Budget Committee 1996-1997 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - NAEP correspondence: Executive Committee Book 4 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - NAEP correspondence: Executive Committee Book 3 1996 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - NAEP correspondence: Executive Committee Book 2 1996 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - NAEP correspondence: Executive Committee Book 1 1996 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - NAEP correspondence: Executive Committee Book 2 1994-1995 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - NAEP correspondence: NEPA Workshop 5/1996 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - NAEP correspondence: brochures & Pamphlets (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - NAEP correspondence: Board Meeting 3/1997 (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - Taiwan #1: The Changing Pacific 10-11/1989 (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Taiwan #1: Final Report on Planning & Development… 1989 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Taiwan #1: 05292.00.006 Publications & Brochures (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Taiwan #1: Final Report, Bound (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Taiwan #1: Related Documents & correspondence (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - HCPs (Habitat Conservation Plans): 1992-1994 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Open Space & Woodlands 1984-1993 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Mining: Regulations, Surface Mining & Reclamation Act 1975 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Mining publications (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - EIR Training: course manuals, handbooks, handouts 1973-1995 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - EIR Training: manuals, handbooks- CEQA, Chinese translations (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - EIR Training: course handouts 1991 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - EIR Training: Coastal planning viewgraphs (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - EIR Training: supporting virographs (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - EIR Training: OCS methodology (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - EIR Training: viewgraphs back-up (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - EIR Training: Spanish viewgraphs (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - GEMS administration: File Index (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - GEMS administration: File Directory (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - GEMS administration: Quick Reference Tools (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - GEMS administration: Computer Tasks (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - GEMS administration: Forms- masters (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - GEMS administration: Projects- Proposals log (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - GEMS administration: NSNET (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - GEMS administration: Attorney/Litigation (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - GEMS administration: Office Space 1997 (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - GEMS administration: Storage (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - GEMS administration: Office Lease (Box 29, Folder 19)
  - GEMS administration: Small Business License (Box 29, Folder 20)
  - GEMS administration: Sacramento Business Property Statement (Box 29, Folder 21)
  - GEMS administration: Business Tax (Box 29, Folder 22)
  - GEMS administration: Bookseller’s Permit (Box 29, Folder 23)
  - GEMS administration: Business Name Records (Box 29, Folder 24)
  - GEMS administration: Employer ID (Box 29, Folder 25)
  - GEMS administration: Inventory Report (Box 29, Folder 26)
  - GEMS administration: Computer (Box 29, Folder 27)
  - GEMS administration: Software (Box 29, Folder 28)
  - GEMS administration: Altima (Box 29, Folder 29)
  - GEMS administration: Answering machine (Box 29, Folder 30)
  - GEMS administration: Fax 1995 (Box 29, Folder 31)
  - GEMS administration: Copier (Box 29, Folder 32)
  - GEMS administration: Fountain pump (Box 29, Folder 33)
  - GEMS administration: Fire extinguisher (Box 29, Folder 34)
  - GEMS administration: Furniture (Box 29, Folder 35)
  - GEMS administration: Postage Meter (Box 29, Folder 36)
  - GEMS administration: Pitney Bowes, PM (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - GEMS administration: Printers (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - GEMS administration: Instruction pamphlets (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - GEMS administration: Security System (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - GEMS administration: Phones (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - GEMS administration: IGC Network (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - GEMS administration: Allnet (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - GEMS administration: Publications (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - GEMS administration: Koozie log (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - GEMS administration: Pro Bono Activities (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - South America: Latin America (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - South America: Tahoe-Andes Partnership (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - South America: Zarate (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - South America: Argentina (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - South America: Brazil (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - South America: Brazil presentations (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - South America: Costa Rica (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - South America: El Salvador (Box 30, Folder 18)
  - South America: Ecuador (Box 30, Folder 19)
  - South America: Guatemala (Box 30, Folder 20)
  - South America: Nicaragua (Box 30, Folder 21)
  - South America: Puerto Rico (Box 30, Folder 22)
  - South America: Uruguay (Box 30, Folder 23)
  - South America: Venezuela (Box 30, Folder 24)
  - South America: Mexico (Box 30, Folder 25)
  - Western Europe: File Index (Box 30, Folder 26)
  - Western Europe: General (Box 30, Folder 27)
  - Western Europe: Iceland (Box 30, Folder 28)
  - Western Europe: Sweden (Box 30, Folder 29)
  - Western Europe: UK (Box 30, Folder 30)
  - Western Europe: Armenia (Box 30, Folder 31)
  - Central & Eastern Europe: CEEBIC (Box 30, Folder 32)
  - Central & Eastern Europe: general (Box 30, Folder 33)
  - Central & Eastern Europe: Belarus 93056 (Box 30, Folder 34)
  - Central & Eastern Europe: Bulgaria (Box 30, Folder 35)
  - Central & Eastern Europe: Czech Republic (Box 30, Folder 36)
  - Central & Eastern Europe: Estonia (Box 30, Folder 37)
  - Central & Eastern Europe: Hungary (Box 30, Folder 38)
  - Central & Eastern Europe: Moldova (Box 30, Folder 39)
  - Central & Eastern Europe: Poland: Institute for Sustainable Development (Box 30, Folder 40)
  - Central & Eastern Europe: Poland: Training P-95040 (Box 30, Folder 41)
  - Central & Eastern Europe: Poland: LEM (Box 30, Folder 42)
  - Central & Eastern Europe: Poland: Regional Environmental Center (Box 30, Folder 43)
  - Central & Eastern Europe: Poland: Landfills, Remediation, Other contracts (Box 30, Folder 44)
  - Central & Eastern Europe: Poland: Risk Assessment (Box 30, Folder 45)
  - Central & Eastern Europe: Poland (Box 30, Folder 46)
  - Central & Eastern Europe: Sarajevo (Box 30, Folder 47)
  - Central & Eastern Europe: Russia/Siberia (Box 30, Folder 48)
  - Central & Eastern Europe: Soviet Environmental Movement (Box 30, Folder 49)
  - Central & Eastern Europe: GEF: INCEIA International NGO Center on EIA (Box 30, Folder 50)
  - Central & Eastern Europe: INCIA (Box 30, Folder 51)
  - Central & Eastern Europe: U.S.-NGO’s (Box 30, Folder 52)
  - Africa: Egypt (Box 30, Folder 53)
  - Asia & S.E. Asia: Pakistan (Box 30, Folder 54)
  - Frontiers (Box 30, Folder 55)
  - Africa: general (Box 30, Folder 56)
  - Africa: Ghana (Box 30, Folder 57)
  - Africa: AxCap (Box 30, Folder 58)
  - Africa: Uganda (Box 30, Folder 59)
  - Western Europe: 05192 Denmark 1992 (Box 30, Folder 60)
  - Asia & S.E. Asia: Damopolii/Indonesia (Box 30, Folder 61)
  - Asia & S.E. Asia: Siberia- Shishkin 1992 (Box 30, Folder 62)
  - Central & Eastern Europe: Slovakia -Kandera 1996 (Box 30, Folder 63)
  - Roberts chronological correspondence 1993 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Roberts chronological correspondence ending 3/9/1995 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Roberts chronological correspondence ending 6/27/95 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Roberts chronological correspondence ending 1/5/1997 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Roberts chronological correspondence ending 6/10/1997 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    Folders 6-16 may contain confidential information.
  - GEMS Personnel: Jens Wessel 1995-1996 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - GEMS Personnel: K. Turkiewicz (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - GEMS Personnel: Angela Butler (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - GEMS Personnel: Nancy MacKenzie 1992-1997 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - GEMS Personnel: Mel Knapp (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - GEMS Personnel: Steve Petersen (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - GEMS Personnel: James Hargrove (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - GEMS Personnel: Ann Bertken (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - GEMS Personnel: Any Feagans (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - GEMS Personnel: Will Pfanner (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - GEMS Personnel: Global Pacific NW- Voss (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - Granite Bay Community Park Project EIR draft 1997 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Granite Bay: appendices (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Granite Bay: appendices (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Granite Bay: memoranda (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - 97007 Pangea Grantmaking Foundations research 1997 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - 97006 Cave Rock 1997 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - EDCWA Water Program EIR suits review- Roberts 1993 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - 97004 PCWA (Placer County Water Agency) working file 1997 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - 97004 PCWA (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - GEMS administration: File Index (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - GEMS administration: “What is EIR?” (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - GEMS administration: Worker’s Compensation (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - GEMS administration: Liability (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - GEMS administration: CORPS permits (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - GEMS administration: Timesheets (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - GEMS administration: Initial Study Form (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - GEMS administration: meeting attendance record (Box 32, Folder 17)
  - GEMS administration: NOP forms (Box 32, Folder 18)
  - GEMS administration: Environmental Document Transmittal form (Box 32, Folder 19)
  - GEMS administration: art (Box 32, Folder 20)
  - GEMS administration: EDD DE-1 registration form (Box 32, Folder 21)
  - 96001 Uganda: draft EIR guidelines & consultancy report 1996 (Box 32, Folder 22)
  - 96001 Background Material (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - 96001 Background Material (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - 96001 Master Report (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - 96001 correspondence in (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - 96001 Contract file (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - 96001 correspondence out (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - 96001 Justin Ecaat (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - EIR Examples: Blue Ravine Parkway, 100-Year Flood Plain, North County Square, Willow Springs, East-Area Folsom, Marlboro Square 1988-1992 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - EIRs examples: American River 1993-1996 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Projects 1995-1996: File Index (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - 95001 Granite Bay: Book #2 1996-1997 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - 95001 Granite Bay: contract file (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - 95001 Granite Bay: proposal memoranda, information file (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - 95001 Granite Bay: blueprints, memoranda (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - 95001 Granite Bay: agency & public comments (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - 95004 Gulf Pacific (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - 95006 USBR Critical needs analysis process (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - 95008 Colton/RM (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - 95009 Jordan action plan (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - 95009 Jordan Marine Pollution Action Plan 1993 (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - 95016 Egypt-Zaire BETEC background (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - 95016 Egypt-Zaire BETEC incoming (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - 95016 Egypt-Zaire BETEC technical reports (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - 95016 Egypt-Zaire BETEC outgoing (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - 95016 Egypt-Zaire BETEC related material: reports, articles (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - ARC data/ESRI (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - 95023 NBO: RMI El Dorado RMP etc. (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - 95023 NBO: RMP miscellaneous correspondence (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - 95026 Slovakia EIA roundtable, 1995 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - 95039 Taiwan Kaoshing Metropark 1996 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - 95041 Mexico Environmental Education & Training 1995 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - 96005 Spain EIS (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - NBD (Global New Business Development): ACCI (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - NBD: ACWA (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - NBD: Aerojet 1997 (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - NBD: Alaska 1996 (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - NBD: Ambiocom 1996 (Box 35, Folder 15)
  - NBD: AT&T (Box 35, Folder 16)
  - NBD: Arcade Water District (Box 35, Folder 17)
  - NBD: BEAC (Box 35, Folder 18)
  - NBD: City/County (Box 35, Folder 19)
  - NBD: California Council on Science & Technology (Box 35, Folder 20)
  - NBD: Chevron (Box 35, Folder 21)
  - NBD: Chisinau- Sacramento Sister City Project (Box 35, Folder 22)
  - NBD: Development Alternatives Inc. DAI (Box 35, Folder 23)
  - NBD: CIWMB (Box 35, Folder 24)
  - NBD: DGV International (Box 35, Folder 25)
  - NBD: Consortia MANNA Ltd. (Box 35, Folder 26)
  - NBD: DOE (Box 35, Folder 27)
  - NBD: El Dorado (Box 35, Folder 28)
  - NBD: ECI (Box 35, Folder 29)
  - NBD: Ecosense (Box 35, Folder 30)
  - NBD: Ecotourism 1995-1997 (Box 35, Folder 31)
  - NBD: A. Fernandez (Box 35, Folder 32)
  - NBD: Glover Stapleton (Box 35, Folder 33)
  - NBD: Harvard (Box 35, Folder 34)
  - NBD: Hawaii (Box 35, Folder 35)
  - NBD: ISO 14000 (Box 35, Folder 36)
  - NBD: Kleinfelder (Box 35, Folder 37)
  - NBD: Kahtilya (Box 35, Folder 38)
  - NBD: M. Kvo (Box 35, Folder 39)
  - NBD: KBI 1996 (Box 35, Folder 40)
  - NBD: Lewis Group AT&T assessments (Box 35, Folder 41)
  - NBD: LML Logistics (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - NBD: LSA Sacramento (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - NBD: Mather Remediation (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - NBD: Meridian (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - NBD: NPS (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - NBD: National Trails (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - NBD: NEC Electronics (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - NBD: Oregon (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - NBD: Pipeline (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - NBD: Population (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - NBD: PTRL (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - NBD: RHAA (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - NBD: Sacramento COM (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - NBD: Systems Approach Lewis (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - NBD: Theo Lacy (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - NBD: Tahoe Baikal (Box 36, Folder 16)
  - NBD: UC Davis MURPPS (Box 36, Folder 17)
  - NBD: VOCA (Box 36, Folder 18)
  - NBD: VSP (Box 36, Folder 19)
  - NBD: Vineyards (Box 36, Folder 20)
  - NBD: Water Education Foundation 1996 (Box 36, Folder 21)
  - NBD: George Wood Association (Box 36, Folder 22)
  - NBD: Yale (Box 36, Folder 23)
  - NBD: Yosemite-Delaware North (Box 36, Folder 24)
  - NBD: Yosemite (Box 36, Folder 25)
  - NBD: Yosemite Institute (Box 36, Folder 26)
  - GEI: File Index (Box 36, Folder 27)
  - GEI: NP Certification (Box 36, Folder 28)
  - GEI: Tax IDs (Box 36, Folder 29)
  - GEI: IRS correspondence 1994 (Box 36, Folder 30)
  - GEI: Bank 1995 (Box 36, Folder 31)
  - GEI: finances 1995-1996 (Box 36, Folder 32)
  - GEI: In absentia lease vote (Box 36, Folder 33)
  - GEI: Mather A/P (Box 36, Folder 34)
  - GEI: Mather- New Site (Box 36, Folder 35)
  - GEI: Programs: Park Development Consultant (Box 36, Folder 36)
  - GEI: County Parks Space Proposal (Box 36, Folder 37)
  - GEI: Lease & Related (Box 36, Folder 38)
  - GEI: HCP (Box 36, Folder 39)
  - GEI: Mather Utilities (Box 36, Folder 40)
  - GEI: City Parks Space Proposal BKI (Box 36, Folder 41)
  - GEI: Board of Directors biographies (Box 36, Folder 42)
  - GEI: Board of Directors correspondence (Box 36, Folder 43)
  - GEI: Board of Directors list (Box 36, Folder 44)